Earlier this year, I introduced you to
Archon, my open source tool as the
world's first agent, an AI agent that
builds other AI agents. But as I was
creating Archon and getting feedback
from all of you, I realized that there
was so much more that I could be doing
with Archon. And so, behind the scenes,
the past few months, me and a few other
guys from the Dynamis community have
been shaping this new vision and
platform for Archon. And I'm super
excited to bring you the beta launch of
that. Right now, we are turning Archon
into the operating system for AI coding
assistance. It's super exciting. I'll
explain in this video what that means
and how you can get started with Archon
yourself today. Now, listen up because
there are some big problems for AI
coding assistance that Archon is aiming
to solve. As powerful as they are, AI
coding assistants almost completely lack
two of the most important components of
context engineering. I'm talking about
rag for our knowledge and documentation
and project management tools like cloud
code and curo. All they have is basic
web search and internal task management
tools that we can hardly interact with.
And so I built archon to solve this and
completely revolutionize the way that we
use AI coding assistants today. And I'm
releasing it as an open-source beta tool
that gives you a full command center to
work with your coding assistants and
collaborate with them at a much deeper
level. Buckle up because in this video
I'm going to give you a demo of Archon.
I'll show you how you can start using it
yourself today. And we'll even have a
conversation with one of the other
maintainers from the Dynamis community,
Shawn Buck. We'll dive into the future
of Archon and our vision for it and how
it relates to context engineering and
all the other stuff that I've been
covering on my channel recently. And I
mean this sincerely. If you are not
hooked on using Archon for all your AI
coding after watching this video, then
I'm just simply not doing my job
conveying the power of this operating
system to you. So, here is the GitHub
repository for Archon, which I will of
course have linked in the description
below. And I'm actually using the
original repository for Archon because
it's very much an evolution of what I
was doing before. So, I just replaced it
with everything that we have here with
the new operating system for AI coding.
So with the new archon, it is a command
center for AI coding assistants. So for
us, it's a sleek interface to manage the
knowledge, context, and tasks for our
projects. And then for the coding
assistant to collaborate on the same
things, it's an MCP server. That's the
beauty of it. The UI is native to
humans. MCP is native to the LLM. So we
each have our way to collaborate on the
same projects together. And then I'll
also in my demo cover all the different
components that we have to archon like
the documentation and rag task
management all that good stuff. And the
other thing that I'll say here is that
my demo in this video is just to get you
started on what's possible with Archon.
If you really want to dive deep with me,
definitely come to the Archon beta
launchparty live stream happening this
Saturday, the 16th at 9:00 a.m. Central
time. I'll actually build something end
to end using Archon to power my
knowledge retrieval and task management.
and it's going to be a good time. So
definitely be there for that live
stream. And one of the things that we've
worked so hard on with Archon is making
it easy for you to get started. So if
you scroll down in the read me here or
you just jump to the quick start, we've
got a very simple guide to get Archon up
and running. So just a couple of
prerequisites that we have here. Docker
desktop, you need a Superbase account
for the database that manages everything
under the hood. And then also an OpenAI
API key for your LLMs and embedding
models. And then also we support Gemini
and Olama. You can run everything
completely locally with Olama with your
own private knowledge base and MCP
server if you want to do so. And so for
the setup instructions here, you just
simply have to clone this repository in
a terminal. Go into the directory here
and then you have to configure your
database and your environment variables.
And so I'll pull up my repo right now
just so I can show you an example of
this. You have your example. You'll just
copy it, rename it to and then fill out
your Superbase URL and Superbase service
ro key. And those are the only required
environment variables to start. And then
we can dive into our database setup. And
so I'll show you this within Superbase
and your Superbase project. You just
have to go to the SQL editor. That's
this tab right here. This is going to
work both for local and hosted
Superbase. So like I said, you can do
everything 100% local if you want to
host Olama and Superbase. So you just go
into the SQL editor and you paste in the
content that I have within this file in
the repository. So this gives you all
the SQL to create all the tables that
Archon uses under the hood to store your
knowledge, your projects, and your
tasks. And then going back here, the
only other thing we have to do is use
Docker to spin up all of our containers.
You just copy this command, go into your
terminal here. I'll just pull this up
and show you and run this command to
build the Archon MCP server, the
backend, and the user interface that we
use to work with our coding assistant.
So here are the default ports that
everything runs on. You can configure
this as well and there's more
instructions on that at the bottom of
the readme. So the first thing we can do
is just go to localhost 3737. That's
going to bring us to this page right
here where we can start configuring
archon. We can crawl the knowledge, set
up the MCP server. That's what I'm going
to walk you through right now. So when
you first go into Archon, the first
thing that you want to do is configure
your settings. So that's the bottom tab
right here. We're also working on an
onboarding flow that'll walk you through
some of this because you need to set
your API key for Google or OpenAI. Or if
you select Olama, which is in progress
right now. We're working on this because
Archon is in beta. Then you don't have
to set an API key at all. And then we
can also copy our IDE global rules. And
so we have global rules crafted for you
to guide your AI coding assistant on how
to leverage archon effectively. And you
can definitely customize these as well.
And so right now these are the ones that
we have for cursor wind surf and cloud
code. We're also working on generalizing
this to make it so it'll apply no matter
your AI coding assistant. You can
definitely just take one of these and
use it for something else like hero or
augment code if you want as well. So you
can just copy these rules and then add
them along with your other existing
global rules. You can just tack this on
to whatever you're already using with
your AI coding assistant. And then
there's a lot of other different
settings that I'll probably talk about
more in the live stream. I don't want to
get into right now, but you're it's very
configurable. It's customizable to you.
And that's one of the things that makes
Archon better than something like
Context 7 because this is your own
private knowledge base. You get to
manage the strategies for Rag and the
way that we're extracting code examples
and things like that. So, you're very
much building your own configurable
private knowledge base, which that's
actually the next thing that I want to
cover here in the knowledgebased tab.
When you add your knowledge with this
button in the top right, there's a lot
of different options that we have here
for the different knowledge sources that
you can add. And then your coding
assistant through the MCP server can
perform rag to search through all of
this documentation and business
knowledge. And so I can give it a URL to
scrape. Like for example, I can have it
scrape the LLM's full.ext for pyantic
AI. So any kind of website, sitemaps,
llms.ext, just full websites that it'll
crawl through recursively. You can give
it all these different kinds of URLs
just like I had in the crawl for AAI rag
MCP server that I've been building on my
channel. I'm incorporating all these
things into Archon just like I said I
would. And you can also upload your own
documents as well. If you want to upload
business documents like PDFs that will
guide the AI coding process, you can do
that. And it's going to chunk those up
and embed those, put them in the
knowledge base for rag just like the
technical URLs for things like library
documentation. And I'll actually show
you what this looks like in real time
here. Like if I just recrawl one of
these, like for example, I've got the
documentation for Pantic AI, mezzero,
langraph, and then cloud code. And I can
rec crawl one of these. I'll show you
just how beautiful this looks. It's so
cool. We have real-time feedback from
the API through these websockets that we
have set up that'll give us the status
of our crawling. So in this case, it
takes that first URL and it actually
using crawl for under the hood. It
recursively goes through, finds all the
different URLs to navigate through to
give us the full documentation. So it
found 44 in total. Now it's crawling
through all of those in batches of five.
And then after it does that, it'll go
through the embedding and chunking
process, getting everything ready for
rag in our Superbase knowledge base. And
so I don't need to show the full process
right here. I definitely encourage you
to play around with Archon yourself.
Like there's anything that I'm not
showing here that you're curious about,
try it yourself. It's so easy to get
started like I showed you. And like I
said, I really hope that it just blows
your mind. And so once you have your
knowledge set up, then you can connect
your MCP server. So you go to the MCP
server tab and here you can see the logs
for your server on the top. You can stop
your server and restart it if you're
doing things like changing your
environment variables. So I'll go ahead
and start it again. Super easy to manage
the MCP. And then we have tabs here to
instruct you on how based on your AI
coding assistant to connect to the
Archon MCP server. And we're working on
expanding this as well to cover
different coding assistants like hero
and augment code and client. So like
winds surf cursor cloud code. I can
click on cloud code because that's the
one that I'm going to be using in my
demo here and we got super simple
instructions. So we just take the cloud
MCP add command, copy this, and I'll use
that in a little bit. But the other
thing I want to show you first is the
project management tab. This is where we
have task management for our AI coding
assistants. And I'll show you one of the
other projects where I'm actually like
in progress here. And the beauty of this
is that the connection that we have here
with us and the UI and the coding
assistant and the MCP server, it is real
time. So while the coding assistant is
running, we can correct things. We can
edit the description of a task. We can
move something back into the backlog and
describe why. And the coding assistant
will have that reflected immediately
when it reads the task the next time.
And as it is doing things, we also get
to see things get populated and moved
around in the UI in real time. And that
really helps us project manage it,
really have that deeper level of
collaboration. like I was saying. And so
let's actually just see this in action.
I've got a new project created for an AI
news agent for the demo that I'm going
to give you here. So we'll go to the MCP
tab. I'll go to cloud code. I'll copy
this command here to add the server.
I'll paste this into my terminal here
that I have running in my IDE. I already
have it added, but otherwise it would
add it for the first time. I can do
cloudm list, which will actually test
our connection to archon as well.
Looking really good. And so what I'm
demoing here, this is an agent that I
actually built in the Dynamis community
for one of our workshops. So it's a
langraph in Padantic AI agentic workflow
that we have here based off of a
prototype that I have in NAND. So I went
through the full PRP process which I'll
link to a video right here if you're
curious to dive into this more. So I
described initially what I want. I used
my execute PRP command to generate this
PRP which is the full spec for what we
want to build. And so I'm going to be
using this plus task management and rag
with archon to build the complete thing.
So I'll go into claude and then I'll
paste in the command to execute this
PRP. So I'll go ahead and kick this off.
And then also for demonstration purposes
in the PRP, I'm telling it to use the
existing project in archon and create
the tasks for the project and perform
rag early on just so for our demo
purposes we can see that happen right
away so I can show you Archon in action.
So I'll pull up archon again. I'll go
back to the project management tab and
then within our news agent here we can
see the tasks start to get populated.
Right now it's listing the projects that
we have in Archon. So it's using the MCP
server and then in a second it's going
to start creating some tasks. So it
finds that we have nothing here. We're
starting the project from scratch. So
there we go. It's going to do some rag
research and then start populating our
tasks. And so I have the knowledge for
podantic langraph already crawled like I
showed you in the knowledge tab. So now
it's performing those queries to get
that information to enhance its code
generations. So there we go. We got 129
results. I can do control-R to expand
this. We can see the different chunks
that it retrieved from this retrieval.
And it's going to look at code examples
as well. There's a couple of different
things. Yep, there we go. Searching for
code examples. There's a couple
different functions that we give it for
more agentic rag to search through our
knowledge base in different ways. And
there's a lot of strategies for rag that
I have built into this under the hood.
And so yeah, I'll pause and come back
once it gets more to the task management
side of things. All right, so there we
go. It created its first task right here
to update the graph state. And I didn't
even have to refresh my page. It's all
in real time thanks to the websockets
that we have here. And there's another
task popping up. The websockets that we
have here between the MCP server and our
user interface. It is such a beautiful
thing. So it's starting to just there we
go. Create all the tasks that we have
here. And then it's going to knock them
out one by one slowly moving them into
in process and then in review, moving on
to the next one. And like I said, we can
update these descriptions and things in
real time, add our own tasks, and it's
going to automatically incorporate those
things without us even having to
interrupt Claude code or your coding
assistant. That is the beauty of it
because a lot of times when you
interrupt a coding assistant, it causes
a lot of problems. It starts to
hallucinate because you cut it off in
the middle of thinking and when you
resume it with another set of
instructions, it's not really in its
natural flow. And so if I update the
task in my interface, then it's going to
pick up those changes when it comes time
to actually get to that task. And so
we're collaborating in a much better way
than just doing an escape or a double
escape here, typing in wherever we want
it to fix, and then having it try to
pick up where it left off and
incorporate that when it makes sense. So
I hope you can kind of see like why this
matters so much that we're able to work
with the coding assistant in a UI and
allow it to be a lot more flexible in
the way that it takes in our feedback
when the time is right. And so yeah,
that's what I wanted to show for Archon
right now. I'm obviously not going to
walk through the full end to end because
I wanted to keep this simple and
definitely come to the live stream if
you want to see me like actually use
this to completion. But yeah, that's
everything that I wanted to show for
Archon right here. Next up, we have a
word from our sponsor, which sponsors
are how I'm able to do these things like
Archon for free for you. Then we'll get
into the conversation with Shawn and
talk more about the vision behind Archon
and the future of it. Now, we've been
talking a lot about Cloud Code in this
video, and it is my favorite AI coding
assistant, but when it comes to building
front-end applications, I still rely a
lot on AI powered app builders like
Lovable or Bolt. New. And that brings us
to the sponsor of today's video, which
is Hostinger, and specifically their
Hostinger Horizon's platform. It's a new
player in the AI app building space
that's been on my radar recently, and
it's really started to impress me. And
what sets Horizon apart is Hostinger is
already your platform for your
professional email, your domain, and
your website hosting. So now you just
have everything under one umbrella,
including with Horizon now, this
beautiful new platform for building our
frontends. And it's just like other AI
app builders where you describe in plain
English what you want. Like here, I'm
having it create a website for my
Dynamus AI mastery community. And then
boom, after a couple of minutes, we have
this beautiful UI created for us, ready
to iterate on and even host. And I
actually took the same prompt and I
compared it with lovable and with bolt
new and I definitely think that
Horizon's won here. Plus, we can edit
the code directly if we want to work
more alongside the coding assistant.
They have integrations with superbase
and with e-commerce. You can build an
online store super easily in Hostinger
Horizons. And also, like I said, it's
very easy to iterate as well. So, for
example, if I want to take this button
and make it actually work, I can just
send in this prompt to have the join
buttons go to my website. And there we
go. 30 seconds later, these links now
work absolutely beautiful. And I can
publish in a single click because I'm
integrated directly within Hostinger
with their domain and website hosting.
And I can even use my own custom domains
like I'm doing right here. So I have
everything hosted on Hostinger built
with Hostinger Horizons. And getting
started could not be easier. I have a
link in the description below. And also
when you use my discount code, you get
10% off your plan. And I'm just showing
you right here really quickly how you
can apply my discount code, which I also
have in the description. Super super
easy. And yearly plans of Horizons also
get free hosting and a free domain. And
so if you've had that app that you've
wanted to build for a while now and you
just haven't found the tool to use it,
definitely check out Hostinger Horizons.
All right, we have the man himself,
Shawn here. And there have been a lot of
amazing people that I've met in the
Dynamis community the past few months,
and Shawn is definitely one of them. So,
he was super interested in Archon
towards its inception and he wanted to
get involved and contribute to a much
larger vision that he brought to me. Um,
Sean is it's he's a visionary and he's
got incredible ideas, a lot of which
you've already seen in the last 5 to 10
minutes in this video here and he's
going to dive into more. Um, and so
yeah, it was just like this immediate
connection that we made um, with the
vision for Archon because I'm more of
like the technical person building out
the back end like you guys have seen
with the first version of Archon and the
crawl for AAI rag MCP and then Sean has
the vision for the UI and the UX and
like really building this into a
beautiful user experience as we're
building this operating system for AI
coding assistance and and what you're
looking at right here. So Sean, why
don't you go ahead and tell us how you
got interested in Archon initially, what
got you involved, and how you've gotten
to where we are now.
>> Thanks, Cole. So, um, yeah, it's it's
exciting to be here. I'm a huge fan of
obviously the Dynamus community being a
part of it. Um, and you know, I came
across I'm a business owner and I
started getting interested in AI. How is
this going to impact my business? Um, I
used to do development in the past and I
used to be in the IT field. Uh, but
being an entrepreneur and a business
owner, I needed to figure this out. And
I came across your channel, oh, probably
almost a year ago now, really in the
early stages. And I I there's a lot of
great content creators out there. But
what attracted me was your view of first
order principles and learning things the
right way. And so I immediately signed
up for Dynamis Community, but what I
didn't expect was all the amazing people
I'd meet. I've met with other business
owners. We're working on projects
together. It's been a lot of fun. But
that Archon video of your original
Archon video really captured me and and
then crawl for AI and what it was doing
on the back end. And I was like, man, if
we just had a really good user interface
that could see what's going on the back
end, people will see how cool what
you're building is. So this is all a
testament to what you built and um I
just hope to contribute to it and
encourage more people to contribute
because this is what we need. We need
people contributing together to build
tools to help us. So that's how I got
interested.
>> Awesome. Yeah, I appreciate it, Sean.
And this definitely is a tool to help
everyone. Like literally, no matter what
you are using AI coding assistance to
help create, this is like the backbone
now for things like the task management
and the knowledge that I've shown you
all in this video already. Like this is
useful no matter what you want to build.
And the other thing I want to say is if
you want to get involved in Archon, you
can do so today. Like it's super easy to
get started. I've got the repo linked
below. And also, I've got the Archon
Beta launch party live stream this
Saturday, the 16th at 9:00 a.m. Central
time. So, I'm going to call it out a few
times throughout this video because I
really want to see you there. So,
definitely be there for the launch of
Archon. I'm going to dive a lot deeper
into using it in action throughout the
stream as well. But with that being
said, I want to dive more into the
vision for Archon now. So, we've
combined things together and I really
want to hear from you, Sean, because
everyone's already heard about my
vision. what's your vision for Archon
and what's led to everything that you've
implemented here?
>> Yeah, so thanks for that Cole and and
and I think ultimately why Archon and
there okay there's tons of coding
assistants out there. There's Gemini,
Clog Code, CL, all CLIs. There's there's
VS Code branches, but how do I keep
control of what everything's going on
when I'm doing development? And what is
consistent for me as I interact with my
agents? And I want to from a user
experience perspective, build more
interactions with agents, not agents
replacing humans, that they're co-pilots
with us, that we're working together.
And I really feel like a lot of people
need to take user experience and user
experience isn't just cool looking UIs
like my Tron-like UI, but it's really
honestly what you did with the crawling
with everything working is also a part
of user experience, but also visual
elements to the user. The vision of
Archon to me should be all things
helping humans and coding assistants
work together. Whether that's working on
your project documents, whether that's
working on your tasks, whether that's
refining your process and the future
with Dynamus Community, what people are
building on to is really cool. Being
able to see what your sub agents are
doing. Um, again, this is really just
about visibility and just if you've ever
been in a point where you're like, I
don't know where my codebase is at.
There's document files all over the
place. Claude created stuff everywhere.
What task are you in on your internal
to-dos? I don't know where you're at.
And that was a frustrating Issa always
had. So that's what we're trying to
solve here. Um, real quick, you'll see
that all of this is an element to help
you interact with that more and give you
visibility. Where are what what's going
on? What's in process? What's been done?
What do I need to review right now? You
can easily kind of interact with this
and be able to see the information and
data. You can copy the task ID and put
it into your MCP. And that's the beauty
of this too is again the MCP is the
interface for the agent. The UI is the
you could use Archon, you know, without
a UI if you want. You could you could
have it go off and still do that with
the MCP, but there's a power in you
seeing the UI and and and being there.
So if you want to work on your documents
together, right, we built in the ability
to uh whether you're having PRPs, you
want to do mobile app development, we
kind of have a nice looking view so you
can interact with it, but even a
markdown editor so you don't have to,
you know, you can just kind of edit your
markdown here. A lot of these cool
things and experiences for you to play
around with. Um, but your agent will
create. It's really cool to see when I
kick off a project and then all of a
sudden it's like, "Oh, let me create the
project at Archon and set all the
tasks." And it puts it in there and I go
look and I'm like, "Yeah, this plan
looks good." It's so much easier for me
to work with than seeing their to-do
list. And this is how we interact with
stuff with with combon boards and task
boards. So, as you can see, I'm using
Archon on a daily basis. And when it
comes to user experience, I believe
people should be users first. if you're
not using your app like that's how you
improve it. So hopefully uh everybody
sees the little features and things that
built in to make interaction a lot
easier. But my projects are working
here. I these are this is actually I'm
about ready to deploy this uh to
production once I finish testing. As you
can see I'm in the testing phase. Um
it's great. It's been extremely helpful
for me. I hope it's helpful for you too.
And I I would just really encourage
people to contribute. uh what are your
talents and skills and let's make Archon
better together and then we all get to
benefit from the use of it.
>> Awesome. I love that Sean. Now, the next
thing that I want to dive in with you,
Sean, I think this is probably the most
exciting is talking about the future of
Archon, cuz I know especially you, I
mean, myself, everyone else that's
getting involved in the Dynamus
community, like we all have our future
vision for Archon, but especially you,
Sean, you have so many incredible ideas
that I've spent a good amount of time uh
listening to you talk about because like
they get me fired up, too. And so the
first one that I want to spend some time
hearing from you about is your ideas of
how we can integrate a lot of the things
we've been doing with context
engineering and like the PRP framework,
how we can integrate that into Archon.
>> Exactly. So, um, as we saw in some of
the demo before, things like the
documents, there's a user interface
there, but being able to start to layer
on more context in the future, like
being able to define what your processes
are, what agents you want to do in
certain checkpoints in a very visual way
that could be then sent to sub aents or
whatever system, but I like to see
things visually. Cloud sub aents have
been great, but reading a bunch of
markdown documents is I don't know which
step goes next and I get confused in
those processes sometimes and sometimes
it kicks off an agent and it wasn't what
I wanted. But I I'm envisioning a cool
view where you can see like a network
chart where they're working and you can
see who's doing what. Um we we've got
some cool people in the Dynamus
community doing stuff with multiple
being able to do local models and and do
local models in parallel. Um, there's a
ton of stuff going on to really help
with context, but I look at context from
a couple different perspectives. You
have sort of your end goal of what
you're trying to achieve. That's sort of
your business context, right? Then you
have the project context for what you're
trying to do here, but you also have
technical context, business knowledge
context. The agents need context for how
they're supposed to operate, like a
development team. Um, and all context
goes many many many levels. It's not
just rag, right? Rag helps with context,
but to me context is just keeping
everybody on the same page. A lot coming
with that. There's a lot of cool people
doing things with subs. And again, our
goal is to not replace those frameworks,
but give you visibility to all those
frameworks and and have a central
command center where you can see what's
going on.
>> Yeah. And that's where I'm excited about
all the and and and if people want to
contribute also, you could contribute on
the public side. But if the Dynamus
community, we're talking about a lot of
cool stuff. A lot of if if this is if
you want to be innovative and you want
to see the next trends or you have a
really good idea, come join us. We're
open to all of this stuff publicly and
in Dynamus.
>> Yeah, definitely. I appreciate that a
lot, Sean. And the really cool thing
with archon is that like you said Sean,
it's not a replacement for these
different strategies like the PRP
framework or spectrum and development or
the BMAD method. It's actually congruent
with those things and we want to build
some of those processes within archon so
it's easier to manage your context as
you're doing those different strategies,
whatever works best for you. Um, and
then the other thing that I I really
want to hone in on with you, Sean, that
you've been talking about already is the
whole idea of sub agents. So tell me
more about like how you envision being
able to manage sub agents within archon
as the operating system.
>> Yeah, so in my IT career I had a long I
was a consultant with agile and helping
teams and development teams work better
together. And I see agents just like
teams people reviewing different work.
In fact with sub agents I see the same
hallucinations actually happen with
humans in corporate world that I see in
sub agents all the time because of lack
of context. And with humans, it's a lot
harder because someone you'll tell
somebody, "Hey, do you understand what I
mean?" And they'll be like, "Yeah, I
understand what you mean, but they
really they really don't." Well, Claude
does the same thing, but it doesn't tell
you, just like we have in the real
world. So, with sub agents, being able
to define them as roles and what they do
and how they hand off to each one one of
another and those interactions is the
context that you need, not necessarily
the technology on the back end. So being
able to like have a character creator
where you could say this is my agent,
you always do this and then you upload
like matrix style upload its knowledge
library and now it it's it but then you
could use any framework whether it's
claude or your own langraph framework or
anything to then these would just be the
definitions of how they would work,
>> right? I love that so much. So, as you
can see, guys, like we have so many
ideas to turn Archon into just an even
more of a masterpiece. And I already
think it it's at that point where like
this it blew my mind when I first saw
some of the things that you were
building, Sean. And and a lot of people
were really excited about some of the
things that I was building at first with
all the rag strategies. And so, we've
got this all combined together. We're
doing a ton of more incredible things
with it. So, you're going to be seeing a
lot more of Sean as he continues to be a
huge part of Archon. And yeah,
definitely come to the launch party that
we got on Saturday. So big things to
stay tuned for, big things to be excited
about. So thank you Sean for for talking
with me about Archon today.
>> Thanks Cole. And just real quick, if
anybody found what I have to talk about
interesting from a business owner
perspective, I am starting my own
YouTube channel, putting myself out
there. It'll be content about this type
of stuff, building things in the real
world and how I do stuff. Uh so come
over. I'd love I'd love to get to know
you.
>> Yes, you guys definitely should. So
thanks Sean. On to the rest of our
video. So, if you've made it this far to
the end of the video, you are definitely
one of the people that I want to have
involved in Archon. Not only do we make
it really easy to use Archon, which I'd
highly recommend you just try it out
today and give us some feedback while
we're in beta, but we also made it
really easy to contribute and be a part
of Archon. We put a lot of effort into
organizing this repository in a really
nice way. We have the GitHub discussions
linked right here so you can be a part
of the conversation. We also created a
contributing guide. So you can read this
just right here in the repo. It gives
you tips on using coding assistance to
help you build out features in Archon,
how to submit PRs, really just all the
resources that you need to contribute.
And so please be a part of this
incredible project that we're building
here. And so if you appreciated this and
you're looking forward to more things on
Archon and trying it out yourself, I
would really appreciate a like and a
subscribe. And with that, I will see you
and the Archon beta launch party live
stream this